<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MySchoolProject</string>
    <string name="app1_name">iQuiz</string>


    <string name="open_nav">Open Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="close_nav">Close Navigation Drawer</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="home">

        JAVA IS A TECHNOLOGY OF CHOICE FOR BUILDING APPLICATIONS +
                 USING MANAGED CODES THAT CAN EXECUTE ON MOBILE DEVICES.\n
                \n
                Android is an open source software platform and Linux-based
                 operating system for mobile devices. The Android platform
                allows developers to write managed code using Java to manage
                and control the Android device. Android applications can be
                 developed by using the Java programming language and the
                Android SDK. So, familiarity with the basics of the Java
                programming language is a prerequisite for programming on
                 the Android platform. This article discusses where Java fits
                 in mobile application development and how we can use Java and
                 Android SDK to write applications that can work on Android devices.\n
                \n
                THE CHOICE OF JAVA\n
                \n
                What made Java be the technology of choice for mobile development for the
                 Android platform? The Java Programming Language emerged in the mid-1990s;
                 it was created by James Gosling of Sun Microsystems. Incidentally,
                 Sun Microsystems was since bought by Oracle.
                 Java has been widely popular the world over,
                primarily because of a vast array of features it provides.
                Java’s promise of “Write once and run anywhere” was one of the major
                 factors for the success of Java over the past few decades.\n
                \n
                Java even made inroads into embedded processors technology as well;
                 the Java Mobile Edition was built for creating applications
                that can run on mobile devices. All these, added to Java’s meteoric rise,
                 were the prime factors that attributed to the decision of adopting
                Java as the primary development language for building
                applications that run on Android. Java programs are secure because
                 they run within a sandbox environment. Programs written in Java are compiled
                into intermediate code known as bytecode. This bytecode is then executed inside
                 the context of the Java Virtual Machine. You can learn more about Java from
                 this link.\n
                \n
                USING JAVA FOR BUILDING MOBILE APPLICATIONS\n
                \n
                The mobile edition of Java is called Java ME. Java ME is based on Java
                SE and is supported by most smartphones and tablets. The Java Platform
                 Micro Edition (Java ME) provides a flexible, secure environment for
                 building and executing applications that are targeted at embedded and
                mobile devices. The applications that are built using Java ME are portable,
                 secure, and can take advantage of the native capabilities of the device.
                Java ME addresses the constraints that are involved in building applications
                that are targeted at mobile devices. In essence, Java ME addresses the
                challenge of executing applications on devices
                that are low on available memory, display, and power.\n
                \n
                There are various ways to build applications for Android devices,
                 but the recommended approach is to leverage the
                 Java programming language and the Android SDK.
                 You can explore more about the Android SDK Manager from here.;


    </string>

    <string name="about">
        About \n

The mission of this company is to help students (and their teachers) practice and master whatever they are learning.
       \n iQuiz provides engaging, customizable activities with contributions from people everywhere.
    </string>

    <string name="subject">

    </string>

    <string name="help">

    </string>

</resources>